You like this? Hey, you like this,
you fucking bitch?
Hey
Hey, do you like it?
You're crying 'cause you like it, right?
Admit it, you like it.
Good? Do you like it?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Fucking bitch
"Proxy Driver"
(Episode 3)
Sleep well?
Let's have some breakfast
I actually made this
for my wife's birthday.
I hope it suits your taste
Give it a try
How is it?
It's good, right?
Try some of this too. Boiled pork
Enjoy your meal.
What's your address?
I'll give you a ride
No, thank you
Just drop me off in front of the station
Are you okay?
I was too much last night, wasn't I?
Let me have a look
No, I'm fine
Let me take a look. Just a quick look!
No, I'm fine. It's nothing.
Let me see
It hurts, fucking bitch.